# **Gianni Naaman**

### Account Manager | Translator | Marketing & Social Media

Address: Dubai, UAE | Phone: +971 05 21138688 | Email: gianni.naaman@gmail.com
Nationality: Lebanese

# Summary

A dedicated and creative account manager with 9+ years of experience in the social media and marketing industries. Proven record of developing, editing, and proofreading engaging content that deliver strong results. Effective leader who performs well in collaborative environment with marketing, advertising, and creative staff. Adept at conducting team and client management, while developing content strategy and brainstorming campaign ideas. Seeking to work in an environment that is conductive to my intellectual, professional, and personal growth, where I can contribute significantly to the growth of the team/organization with strong experience and expertise leading to success.

## Experience

### Senior Content Executive – 11/2021 to Present

Publicis Media, Dubai, UAE

- Successfully cooperate and communicate within the team, coordinate communications between the client & Marketing & Content department while managing a team of copywriters and multimedia designers to deliver content for Dubai Tourism GCC
- Create the content calendar, oversee monthly and listening reports, while working on and implementing a comprehensive content strategy for the account to be up to date in the ever-evolving social landscape
- Introduce new content formats such as cinemagraphs, infographics, Instagram guides and reels, while solidifying the brand's presence on TikTok with over 25 million views and increasing user engagement by 60%
- Adhere to a content strategy that assists marketing and communications initiatives, while working with marketing and communications specialists to determine which methods will best help to achieve goals
- Deliver clear, concise and easily searchable audience appropriate content, accurately reflecting business intent and maintaining integrity and company standards to improve agent navigation of policy and procedure

#### Freelance Translator – 06/2015 to 08/2022

- Translates various types of documents from Arabic to English and English to Arabic
- Provides subtitles for Youtube videos

#### **Content Executive** – 07/2019 to 10/2021

Publicis Media, Beirut, Lebanon

- Make sure that all content is on-brand, consistent in terms of style, quality and voice in order to produce a
  consistent user experience across all channels while increasing the inbound queries by 129% and brand
  engagement by 84% and 83% in video views
- Create a functional editorial/content calendar to be shared with organizational stakeholders and content
  creators to actively and effectively produce content on a strategic schedule, while increasing assets and key
  messages for the greatest return
- Identify new content opportunities from incoming story ideas, organizational and professional current events, regional and national news, trends and matters of interest
- Train and direct staff content producers while serving as an arbiter of best practices in grammar, messaging, writing, and style, and ensuring proper formatting, tagging and categorization of content
- Collect and produce website materials, sustain and develop quality information to the audience, while
  ensuring that the content published is in accordance with standard rules and regulations

Social Media Manager – 12/2016 to 06/2019 Interactive Pod, Lebanon

- Successfully oversee several seasons of Maybelline's Middle East show on Youtube Makyaj wa Banat, add
  English subtitles on the videos while kicking off several brand's presence on several social media channels
  such as Facebook, Instagram & Youtube
- Monitor and review online feedbacks while coordinating with marketing, communications and PR team to enhance brands' consistency and developing copies for more than 8 brands in both English and Arabic
- Assist in the design, branding, and structure of the company as well as the business development from a
  marketing approach while creating comprehensive social media programs that support the brand strategy to
  increase brand visibility
- Plan and develop associate work schedules, allocate tasks and delegate work, monitor job progress and workflow, while overseeing work for timeliness and accuracy, and appraising work performance
- In charge of all daily correspondence including phone calls, email, walk-in traffic and website requests, while
  also being responsible for analyzing interactions for customer sentiment to further refine the target
  audience

Freelance Community Manager – 05/2018 to 09/2018 Havas, Lebanon

Freelance Translator – 08/2016 to 12/2016 Cinemoz, Beirut, Lebanon

Freelance Translator – 09/2016 to 12/2016 Image Production House, Beirut, Lebanon

Translation Internship – 03/2016 to 05/2016 Joelle Aziz Translation Firm, Jdaideh, Lebanon

Account Executive – 10/2013 to 09/2015 Accelerate Online, Furn El Chebbak, Lebanon

### Education

#### **Bachelor of Art in Translation - 2017**

American University of Science and Technology (AUST), Beirut, Lebanon

### Certificates

Facebook Creative Strategy Professional Certificate – Meta
The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Certificate – Google Digital Garage
Snapchat Ads Manager Certificate – SNAPFOCUS
Strategic Thinking Certificate – LinkedIn
Twitter Flight School Video Badge Certificate – Twitter
Proficiency in English Certificate – University of Michigan

# Skills & Expertise

- Leadership & Team Management
- Communication & Negotiations
- Market Research
- Entrepreneurship & Business Development
- Problem Solving
- Project Management
- Customer Service

- Organizational Skills
- Employee Training
- Public Relations
- Content Strategy
- Social Media Management
- Microsoft Office
- Creativity

# Languages

Arabic: Native | English: Fluent | French: Advanced